Mészáros Sámuel

Contact:

E-mail: meszaros.samuel.official@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/s%C3%A1muel-m%C3%A9sz%C3%A1ros-54150821a/

GitHub: https://github.com/sm-samax

Objective:

It is more than 5 years since I have become passionate about computer science. Initially I modified games and repaired malfunctioning computers. Afterwards, in the university I learnt a lot about OOP and design principles, along with quality assurance. In addition, I had the luck to work wih professional software engineers, where I found myself achieveing better in the backend. I like getting touch with people and help their way with my knowledge or take their advice.

Skills:

- Java (Spring Boot)
- SQL (PostgreSQL, MySQL)
- NoSQL(MongoDB, Neo4J)

- JavaScript (Angular, React)
- Python (Tensorflow)
- Version controlling (Git)

Projects:

- Stripe payment (<u>link</u>)
- Spring MVC webshop (link)

- Pinterest remake (link)
- Toxicity classifier (link)

Education:

2016-2020 - Highschool of Senta - General major

2020-present – Faculty of Sciences, Novi Sad – Department of Mathematics and Informatics – Information technology major

Certifications:

July 20, 2021 - Oracle University - Oracle Certified Professional: Java SE 11 Developer

Experience:

2019-present – Freelancing – Computer service (virus removal, OS repair etc.)

2022-present – JUSOFT Hungary Ltd. – Java backend developer

Languages:

Hungarian

- English
- Serbian